https://www.usdermatologypartners.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
U.S. Dermatology Partners respects your privacy and the security of your personal information. We are committed to protecting your privacy through our compliance with this policy. Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. By accessing or using our website, you agree to this privacy policy.
Types of Information Collected
Personal Information
We may collect your personal information, such as your name, email address or telephone number, when you provide it to us directly in a form. We will never collect this information without your knowledge or consent, and we will never sell this information.
Usage Details
We may automatically collect data on your IP addresses, internet connection, operating system, browser and equipment. As you navigate through our site, we may also collect information about your browsing patterns, such as traffic data, location data, logs, other communication data and resources accessed.
The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not identify any individual. It helps us to improve our site and to deliver better and more personalized future services.
Advertisements
U.S. Dermatology Partners may use third party vendors, including Google, which serves the Google Trusted Store badge and other advertisements based on a user’s prior visits to our website. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our website, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. Find further information regarding the privacy practices of our advertisement provider here.
Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page.
Our Promise
We will never sell your personal information or provide it to others for marketing purposes.
To ask questions or give us feedback regarding this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact your local U.S. Dermatology Partners practice. Find your local practice by searching for a location.
Ready to Get Started?
Sign Up for Our Newsletter!
Get the latest updates on news, specials and skin care information.
Email*
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms.
